Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable to harness mana, was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's Dark Triad also possessed powers from the devils of the Underworld,
and used them to launch an invasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself and from the support of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for the safety of this world.
In a fierce battle, Yami and Asta defeated Dante.
Looks like we haven't lost after all.
Then, Xenon appeared and took Yami away, along with Captain William Bonchance.
Captain Yami, no!
That night, when Asta tried to sneak away from the Infirmary Tower to save Yami,
he met someone new.
It was Noct, Vice-Captain of the Black Bulls.
I can teach you how to use your devil power.
If you would like to learn, that is.
Noct carried Asta to the emergency captain's meeting.
Tell us, who are you?
This man is with the Black Bulls.
He's their Vice-Captain.
He'd been operating in the Spade Kingdom as a spy.
However, I was unaware that he was possessed.
Meanwhile, in the Spade Kingdom, the ritual to bring about the advent of Kleefoth was underway.
At its completion, a path would be open to the underworld.
And Yami and Bonchance, who were being offered as sacrifices, would lose their lives in the process.
In three days, the first of seven gates to the underworld will open.
Unless the Dark Triad is stopped before then.
In that case, we'd better reach out to Heart for assistance as well.
I've tried, but they haven't answered me all day.
For a moment, it seemed as though Vanica's magic had decimated the Heart Kingdom.
I don't believe it.
Get it on, get it on,始めよう!
難航不楽のリアリティ
立ち止まる時間はないさ
Hold on, hold on!
Yeah!
7,5,4,リバティ
真実性 飲み込め 常識 覚え
逆境の先にある朝
Oh, yeah!
幻想に埋もらえた 人生の夢
Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Louder!
Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it!
Never give up!
限界を超えて もうかすぐして
Experience!
We cannot pay!
Let's go!
Believe in myself!
衝動的に突き進め Don't be afraid
誰よりも高く飛べ Take it to the sky
想像を超えた 世界をこの手に
The ground up!
想像せよいつはいどない 自分の道
Yes! It's a ground up!
Hey, yeah!
Believe in myself!
Yeah!!
Yeah!
The 홍alindor
This is crazy.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun's leader, and the Elves from the Third Eye?
You guys...
Where are we?
This is Elysia, a secluded part of a strong magic region, deep within the Heart Kingdom.
The mana here is incredibly dense.
Oh, so they're awake.
Who are those two?
These children are the descendants of Licht and the Clover Kingdom's Princess Tatia.
Back then...
Lady Tatia...
She's...
Still alive.
Judging by this mana, one of the twins she was carrying must have survived as well.
As soon as I realized that, I sealed Lady Tatia's wounds. Then I rushed to the Prince's side.
After that...
I woke up in the form of a bird. Many years had gone by. I had no idea what had become of the Princess.
But she made it. Despite everything, her life was saved. The children of an Elf and a Human.
Prince Lumiere. The lives you always hoped for. The new world you wished for. They're here.
The place that we're in is the new home of the Elves. When we found it, I felt as though I understood the reason we stayed behind in this era.
I hope I'm not overstepping, but why did you decide to rescue us?
We received a divine word. From Dryad, the guardian deity who protects Elysia.
Guardian deity?
We were told to help you. We rushed to the Heart Kingdom as soon as we heard. But we were too late.
Thankfully...
All of you had somehow used your own powers to survive those massive explosions.
We had already gone.
Let's move on.
Please start.
Because of you, the citizens of the Hard Kingdom were saved.
I'm amazed that you were able to persevere against foes like them.
You've clearly become much stronger of late.
Persevering isn't enough.
After all of those months of training, I should have been able to defeat them and make sure the world was safe for good.
Now that they've got Laura Petschka, who knows what's going to happen to her?
That's why.
We all need to build our fighting skills! And quickly!
The four of you are even better mages than we are, correct?
So tell me how you got that way right now!
Look at you. Is that really the proper way to ask someone to help, Little Miss Royalty?
You're lost to these enemies after months of hard training.
And you think if you grow a bit more, that you'll be able to win?
Not exactly. I know it's not that easy.
But giving up would be even more impossible for me!
We'll try!
Right, everyone?
That's right!
I see.
You guys are still a pain, like you always were.
Then, we'll teach you an elven art.
Ultimate magic. That should help you.
I can't stop worrying.
I sure hope Charmy and the others are okay.
Gaja!
All right. I think I'm up to speed.
We're attacking Spade in three days, in the early morning hours.
What will you do?
Our forces will fight with you.
All of the spirit guardians are safe.
On the honor of the heart kingdom, we will rescue our queen.
Lady Noelle and the others are preparing to re-enter the fray.
Whether they make it in time depends on them.
Understood. Thank you for reaching out to us.
I will save you.
No matter what.
I refuse to let them take his life.
Wait for me, Yami.
Well, on the bright side, Charmy, the other magic knights, and spirit guardians are all safe.
Sounds like they're training some more.
It's time for me to get back to it.
Vice-captain!
Yeah, that's weird.
Where did you go?
In three days, we'll gather the most elite of the magic knights and initiate an attack against the Spade Kingdom.
I'm sorry.
You're the vice-captain of the Black Bulls?
If that's true, then why have we never seen you before?
Simply put, it's because I hate the Black Bulls.
I'm content as long as I can still be a magic knight.
Being a vice-captain is convenient because I can do as I please.
I despise people who can't do things properly, and the Black Bulls are a squad with a reputation for creating more problems than they solve.
You may have done well in the battle six months ago, but that doesn't even begin to erase all your past failures.
The Witch with a drinking problem.
The Spatial Mage whose philandering interfered with countless missions.
The ex-noble slash convict.
And as for the ones who aren't around at the moment,
you've got an evil-looking delinquent commoner, and another evil-looking delinquent commoner just like him, except he wears a mask.
The point is that your good-for-nothing captain built a team of losers.
But all of them are wonderful people!
You shouldn't judge them because of the way they look!
If you don't want to be judged by your looks, then you need to change the way you present yourself.
Sometimes, those who seem evil or have a history of evil deeds will do something good, making them more likable.
But that is disgusting to me.
I vastly prefer people who are good from the start.
And that doesn't apply to any of you.
If you still want to save that worthless man's life, you have two days to improve your skills.
I've been meaning to ask, what's your magic?
Shadow magic.
It moves my body and anything I touch from one shadow to the next.
Awesome. So it's kind of like portals, then?
Here we are.
A house?
Whose place is this?
It was a noble's house.
Well, former noble.
Here.
What's the deal, man?
What are we doing?
Shadow magic.
Dark garden invitation.
Where the heck are we?
For the next two days, I'll teach you everything I know about using the power of devils.
And your capabilities are going to grow exponentially.
So it's time to train, then?
Sweet, let's go!
As it stands, you aren't using your devil's might to its full potential.
Merely the scraps of excess power that happen to trickle down from it.
This is unorthodox, but it does work.
To give you complete command, we'll perform a devil-binding ritual, a forbidden ceremony that requires you to make a formal deal with your devil.
Devil-binding?
Once we do that, its full power will become yours.
First, we need a connection to the devil.
Normally, you'd use a relic like what I have.
Something like this would temporarily allow you to summon the being from inside your body to our world.
But you seem to be a special case.
Your arm, your grimoire, in fact, your very existence has a unique and profound connection to that devil.
Right.
So, how am I supposed to do it?
Summon.
What?
The devil.
My arm.
How about that?
I wasn't expecting you to let me out on your own.
Now it's time to fight him, and win.
Use your powers to bend him to your will.
That's the only way to harness his full strength.
It's been a while since I got to stretch my legs.
This is weird.
I can't believe he's standing right here in front of me.
There's something I've wanted to tell you for a long time.
Thanks a bunch!
That's right, you heard me.
I can't even count how many times you've helped me in a fight.
Right here.
Right now.
I'm going to push past my limit!
Pass us right now.
This is it.
All I've got.
I never would have been able to win all those crazy battles without your help.
I seriously can't thank you enough for that.
Wow!
So I take your right arm and you thank me?
Well, that was the bargain, wasn't it?
I can't really complain.
You're even more of a hopeless idiot than I thought you would be.
I guess it doesn't matter, though, because you're about to be a dead idiot.
Not gonna happen!
Anyway, I just remembered our first conversation.
A half-out like you doesn't stand a chance in this fight.
You're just as short as I am, though!
From the way you were talking, I thought you would be a giant.
I'm not gonna get my butt kicked by the likes of you!
You really have no idea what kind of mess you've gotten yourself into, do you?
Demon Slayer.
I told you, you'll never beat me!
Whoa!
Now that you've let me into your world, I've got the advantage!
And I want more than your arm!
This time I'm going after every last bit of you!
He's up for a second!
I don't want to fight you, okay?
I want to talk!
You'll fight him.
Your intention is to make yourself stronger, isn't that right?
That means you'll have to face and defeat your devil.
Right now.
If you lose, he'll take over and turn you into a vicious monster.
What?
The skulls you see on the altar belong to those who failed the devil-binding ritual.
If you don't do this, I'll dispose of you and add you to their ranks.
Hang on.
Isn't this forbidden magic?
This ritual thing.
Is it something we're not supposed to be doing?
We only have two days.
Did you really think you could win playing by the rules?
You wanted to grow your skill despite having no magic.
This is the world you stepped into.
What are you doing?
At this rate, you'll be killed for sure.
No.
It's okay.
I know from his key he's not trying to kill me.
I can tell.
Have you lost your mind?
You're dealing with a devil, remember?
Creatures like him don't have principles.
Got that right.
Trust me on this.
Every devil you'll ever meet is a piece of shit like me.
This guy's different from the one I fought back then.
I can't wait to take control of your whole body.
Just because you're a devil,
that doesn't automatically mean you're an evil being at heart.
Damn it.
I know the truth.
You're not a bad guy.
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
夜明け前の空 静かにそっと
ほら新たな日々が始まる
胸にしまい込んだままの
想いを解き放って
その翼を広げて
No more time
今飛び立て
あの海原を見下ろして
誰よりも遠く
何度でも
We'll fly
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful
どんな景色も
君といれば輝くよ
だからずっとそばにいて
And never let go
The world is so beautiful.
Clover Police
Vice Captain
You know, it's a little bit weird that we don't have a Vice Captain.
Yeah, but it kind of makes sense when you think about who our boss is.
Working for him is not for the faint of heart.
If they wanted to drink with him, they'd have to be able to hold their liquor.
And believe me, they'd need to be quick on their feet to handle all those crazy requests.
I think it would have to be someone with lots of strength and courage to stand by him in battle.
And of course, his number two would have to wait around for him to take a number two.
I guess that's why we don't have one.
I hate that squad.
I hate them.
In this place where magic is everything, there lives one boy who was born without it.
Despite the many challenges he faces, he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Black Clover, page 170, the faraway future.